[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service is defined as 'virtual machines inside AWS'?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail",
        "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["EC2"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service allows you to run and manage docker containers at scale?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["EC2 Container Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service provides autoscaling groups, load balancers, EC2 instances, and allows developer to only have to focus on their code?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elastic Beanstalk"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service allows you to upload your code to the cloud and control when it executes, not worrying about underlying physical or virtual machines or OSs?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "Lambda", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Lambda"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service allows you to use a Virtual Private Server (VPS)?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["LightSail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service provisions a server, gives you a fixed ip address, rdp (windows) or ssh (linux) login shell access, and has its own management console?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["LightSail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service is thought of as 'a watered down version of EC2?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "LightSail", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["LightSail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS compute service gives you batch computing in the cloud?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Beanstalk", "Batch", "EC2", "EC2 Container Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Batch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS storage service gives you object based storage in the cloud based on 'buckets'?",
      "answers": ["S3", "Elastic File System (EFS)", "Glacier", "Snowball", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS storage service gives you network attached storage and can mount these to multiple EC2 instances?",
      "answers": ["S3", "Elastic File System (EFS)", "Glacier", "Snowball", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elastic File System (EFS)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS storage service gives you data archival?",
      "answers": ["S3", "Elastic File System (EFS)", "Glacier", "Snowball", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glacier"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS storage service gives you a way to bring large amounts of data into AWS and is used for TB sized transfers instead of using broadband or wireless?",
      "answers": ["S3", "Elastic File System (EFS)", "Glacier", "Snowball", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowball"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS storage service is a virtual appliance/machine that you install in your data center that replicates data into S3?",
      "answers": ["S3", "Elastic File System (EFS)", "Glacier", "Snowball", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Storage Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS database service gives you MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server, PostgreSQL, Aurora, and Oracle databases as a managed service?",
      "answers": ["Elasticache", "RDS", "Red Shift", "DynamoDB", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["RDS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS database service gives you a NoSQL database as a managed service?",
      "answers": ["Elasticache", "RDS", "Red Shift", "DynamoDB", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["DynamoDB"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS database service gives you a way of caching commonly queried data from your database?",
      "answers": ["Elasticache", "RDS", "Red Shift", "DynamoDB", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elasticache"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS database service gives you data warehousing or business intelligence?",
      "answers": ["Elasticache", "RDS", "Red Shift", "DynamoDB", "Storage Gateway"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Red Shift"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service gives you tracking service allowing you to track your applications as you migrate them to AWS?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Migration Hub"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service integrates with other services within the migration framework to help you keep track of application and database migration activity and also has a visualization of all migration activity?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Migration Hub"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service gives you an automated set of tools which detect what applications you have and what their dependencies are?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Application Discovery Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "21",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service gives you a way of tracking application dependencies?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Application Discovery Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "22",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service gives you an easy way to migrate your databases from on-premise to AWS?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Database Migration Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "23",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service gives you a way to migrate virtual and physical servers from on-premise to AWS?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Server Migration Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "24",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS migration service is used for migrating large amounts of data to AWS?",
      "answers": ["Database Migration Service", "Server Migration Service", "Snowball", "AWS Migration Hub", "Application Discovery Service"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowball"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "25",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service gives you a virtual data center?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["VPC"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "26",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service is Amazon's Content Delivery Network (CDN)?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudFront"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "27",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service allows you to store content closer to users around the globe using Edge Locations?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudFront"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "28",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service is Amazon's DNS service?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Route 53"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "29",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service gives you a way of creating APIs for other services to talk to?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["API Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "30",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS network and content delivery service gives you a way of running a dedicated line from your on-premise data center to your AWS VPC?",
      "answers": ["Route 53", "CloudFront", "VPC", "API Gateway", "Direct Connect"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Direct Connect"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "31",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool gives you a way of getting a group of developers working together to 'project manage' their code?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Star"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "32",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool contains a delivery tool chain?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Star"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "33",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool provides a source control service where you can store your private git repositories?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Commit"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "34",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool allows you to compile your code, run tests, and produce software packages that are ready to deploy?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Build"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "35",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool automates application code deployment to your EC2 instances or on-premise instances, as well as to your lambda functions?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Deploy"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "36",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool provides a continuous delivery service, where you can model, visualize, and automate the steps required to release your software?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Code Pipeline"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "37",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool is used to deploy and analyze your serverless application code and has request tracing to help find issues and performance bottlenecks?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["X-Ray"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "38",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS developer tool gives you an IDE to develop code within the AWS console?",
      "answers": ["X-Ray", "Cloud9", "Code Pipeline", "Code Deploy", "Code Build", "Code Commit", "Code Star"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Cloud9"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "39",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool provides you with a monitoring service for your AWS resources?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudWatch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "40",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool gives you a way of scripting infrastructure and deployment of infrastructure?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudFormation"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "41",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool gives you a way to turn infrastructure into code?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudFormation"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "42",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool is used to log changes to you AWS environment and stores its records for one week?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudTrail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "43",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool monitors the configuration of your entire AWS environment?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Config"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "44",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool has point-in-time snapshots of your AWS environment and visualizes your AWS environment over time past through present?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Config"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "45",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool uses both Chef and Puppet to automate your environments and the configuration of your environments?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["OpsWorks"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "46",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool manages a catelog of your account resources that are approved for use in your AWS account?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Service Catalog"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "47",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool is used for governance and compliance requirements for your AQS account?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Service Catalog"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "48",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool gives you an interface for managing your AWS resources?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Systems Manager"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "49",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool is used for EC2 for things like patch maintenance?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Systems Manager"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "50",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool would you use to install a patch across thousands of EC2 instances all at once?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Systems Manager"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "51",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool gives you advice around security, cost optimization, performance, and fault tolerance?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Trusted Advisor"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "52",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS management tool lets AWS manage your EC2 instances, auto-scaling, load balancers, etc?",
      "answers": ["CloudWatch", "CloudFormation", "CloudTrail", "Config", "OpsWorks", "Service Catalog", "Systems Manager", "Trusted Advisor", "Managed Services"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Managed Services"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "53",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service transcodes videos so they appear correctly across all device types?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elastic Transcoder"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "54",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service is a file based video transcoding service?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["MediaConvert"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "55",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service is live video processing service?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["MediaLive"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "56",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service prepares and protects videos for transfer over the internet?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["MediaPackage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "57",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service is a storage service that's optimized for video?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["MediaStore"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "58",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS media service allows targeted advertising in video streams?",
      "answers": ["Elastic Transcoder", "MediaConvert", "MediaLive", "MediaPackage", "MediaStore", "MediaTailor"],
      "correctAnswer": ["MediaTailor"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "59",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service makes it easy for developers to use deep learning (neaural networks) when coding their applications?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["SageMaker"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "60",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service does sentiment analysis of your data?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Comprehend"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "61",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service is an artificially aware camera that can figure out what it's looking at using deep learning?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["DeepLens"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "62",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service is service that powers Alexa?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Lex"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "63",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service provides an artificially intelligent chat capability?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Lex"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "64",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service is a less sophisticated 'learning' tool than deep learning that uses data set analysis to predict outcome when new data sets are applied to it?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Machine Learning"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "65",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service is the service that Amazon uses to recommend new products to its users?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Machine Learning"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "66",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service takes text and turns it into speech?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Polly"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "67",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service provides video and image contect recognition?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Rekognition"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "68",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service is Amazon's machine translation service which translates one language into another?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Translate"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "69",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS machine learning service automates speech recognition to produce transcription of video audio?",
      "answers": ["SageMaker", "Comprehend", "DeepLens", "Lex", "Machine Learning", "Polly", "Rekognition", "Amazon Translate", "Amazon Transcribe"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Transcribe"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "70",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service allows you to run SQL queries against data in your S3 buckets?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Athena"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "71",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is used for processing large anounts of data for big data solutions that uses many servers (running hadoop) to chop up your data for analysis?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["EMR"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "72",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service manages all the server resources needed to build and deploy search indexes. All you have to do is upload your data to a search domain and start submitting requests?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudSearch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "73",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is a popular open-source search and analytics engine for use cases such as log analytics, real-time application monitoring, and clickstream analytics?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elasticsearch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "74",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is a way of ingesting large amounts of data into AWS , like social media feeds or tweets?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Kinesis"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "75",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is a way of ingesting video streams and do processing on the data?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Kinesis Video Streams"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "76",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is Amazon's business intelligence tool, similar to Tableau?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["QuickSight"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "77",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service gives you a way of moving your data between different AWS services?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Data Pipeline"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "78",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Define AWS Cloud",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS analytics service is used for Extract/Transform/Load types of analytics processing?",
      "answers": ["Athena", "EMR", "CloudSearch", "Elasticsearch", "Kinesis", "Kinesis Video Streams", "QuickSight", "Data Pipeline", "Glue"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glue"]
    }
  }
]
